bitconnect.co 2017-02-04

# Privacy Policy | Bitconnect

##### LAST UPDATED FEB 15, 2016

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) describes the collection, use & disclosure of information collected online by our website at www.bitconnect.co. We are committed to maintaining the security & confidentiality of your personal & financial information.As you review our policy, keep in mind that it applies to all Bitconnect.co products & services that do not have a separate privacy policy. 

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. We are not responsible for the protection & privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites & such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution & look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

We collect personal & financial information from you while you use the site, & most of this collection occurs during registration. Some information is required & some is optional, some will remain private & some will be displayed to other users. We always let you know which information will remains private & which will be displayed to other users. By visiting Bitconnect.co website you agree & consent to the practices described in this privacy policy. 

## Which information collected?

You will be required to submit sensitive information and proof of identity to unlock our modules and use the various servcies, specifically:

### Personal information supplied during registration process

We collect your full name, email address, mobile number, date of birth, in order to enable registered bitconnect.co members to login to the site.

### Personal information supplied to update public profile

We also collect content & information updated in public profile when you use our services, including information about you, your work & education, photo of you & content you uploaded to bitconnect site.

### Personal information submitted to increase trustworthiness of your public profile

We collect your personal identity proof, your address proof to verify your true identity. This information will not be disclosed to other community member or third party.

### Your networks & connections to other bitconnect community members

We collect information about the people you are connected to & how you interact with them, including information about shared content with other community members.

### Information about third party social connections

We collect information about third party social connections like Facebook, Google+, LinkedIn & Twitter to increase the trustworth level of your Bitconnect profile.

### Information about Bitcoin payments

We collect information about your personal bitcoin addresses you linked with Bitconnect site.

### Device information

We collect information from or about the computers, phones, or other devices where you access our services, depending on the permissions you’ve granted.

### Information by third party

When you use the Website, website's servers (which may be hosted by a third party service provider) may collect information indirectly & automatically about your activities on the Website; for instance by way of cookies.

## How do we use this information?

We use the information to create a composite profile of our valuable members, so they can utilize our service modules. Membership does not guarantee access all modules. We use this information collected to connect you to trusted members of community by analyzing their profile information submitted to Bitconnect system

We use your information to communicate with you occasionally about our services, promotions, local events&to inform you of updates to our policies, terms&conditions. Beyond profile analysis, we use your information for replies when you contact us. Location information, if provided, will be used to tailor our Services for community members to find local events or meet-up in your area.

Safety is our number one concern. We use the information submitted to help verify members accounts & activity, &for the continued hardening of security of our services, including but not limited to investigating suspicious activity or violations of our terms or policies, abuse of our services, evidence of Sybil accounts, ban evasion, any attempts to defraud or otherwise circumvent the prevention mechanism & spam. We work hard to protect your account using a culmination of talented engineers, automated systems, & advanced technology such as encryption & machine learning mechanisms to audit activity in real-time. Finally, we provide easy-to-use security tools to add an extra layer of security on accounts. 

## How is the information shared?

Members use our services to connect with other community members. We share your information in following ways:

### People you share & communicate with

When you share or communicate using our services, you choose the level of profile visibility.To set visibility simply set the audience view level when editing your account profile. This feature also works when making posts on the network with current options being either public or friends while using our service. Public information is available to anyone who accessed through our services & online search engines. In some cases, people you share & communicate with may download or share this content (including media) with others on & off our services.

### People that see content others share about you

Other members may use our Services to share content about you with the audience they choose. For example, people may share a photo of you, share posts you make on your public profile, or share information about you that you shared with them.

### We share your information during bitcoin lending

We share your screen name, mobile number, & bitcoin addresses with other bitconnect community members while you make lend or redeem requests in the system. For privacy purposes, members remain anonymous on the site & are identified only by their chosen screen names.

### We share your information during bitcoin trading

We share your screen name, mobile number, & bitcoin addresses to other bitconnect community members while you make buy or sell bitcoin request in the system. For privacy purposes, members remain anonymous on the site & are identified only by their chosen screen names. However, members have their public profile on Bitconnect system that displays their information to any members who view these pages.

### We share your information during selling E-commerce products

We share your screen name & bitcoin addresses to other bitconnect community members while you make product selling request in the system. For privacy purposes, members remain anonymous to their real life identification on the site & are identified only by their chosen screen names. Keep in mind that members have their public profile on Bitconnect system which should be used to evaluate the trustworthiness of the vendor!

### We share your information with trusted third parties

Bitconnect works with a number of trusted partners that perform vital functions as part of our operations, bitcoin payment service providers, & customer support mechanisms. Information is shared with these third parties only to the extent necessary for us to process the transactions you initiate or perform other specific services. Our partners are legally required to keep your information private & secure. We will never ask you for private keys or sensitive account information such as passwords.

### Controlling your personal information

We will not sell, distribute, disclose, nor lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your explicit permission or are required by law to do so in the case of a legal investigation.

## How can you manage or delete information about you?

Use the Activity Log Tool to manage the content & information you share with Bitconnect. We will retain your information as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you products & services. Information associated with your account profile will be kept until your account is deleted. You can delete your account any time. When you delete your account, we delete things you have posted, such as your photos & status updates. To set your account as inactive & temporarily suspend services, please enable holiday mode on your profile settings page instead. Keep in mind that information that others have shared about you is not part of your account &may not be deleted when you delete your account.
